http://www.ufcu.org/policies-legal/privacy-policy

How can we help?
ask a question or search
contact us
talk to us on a social network
popular topics
Routing NumberLoan RatesOrder ChecksDirect DepositMobile BankingOnline BankingChange PasswordUT PayrollWire TransfersCareers
Call
Austin: (512) 467-8080 Galveston: (409) 797-3300 US Toll-Free: (800) 252-8311 TTY: (512) 421-7477 All Numbers
Photos and Short Videos
How can we help?
popular searches
Alert:
Our Ben White location is temporarily closed. Read More. You also can review our Quick Service Guide to find out how we can best serve you.
Bylaws
What does University Federal Credit Union do with your Personal Information?
Why?
Financial Institutions choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and income
account balances, account transactions and payment history
credit history, credit scores and insurance claims history.
When you are no longer our customer, we discontinue sharing of your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial institutions need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial institutions can share their customers' personal information; the reasons University Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
UFCU does not sell our
members' personal information, nor do we condone or endorse the use of personal information we share with third parties for any purpose than for acting on behalf of UFCU and strictly for the benefit, service or education of our members.
Reasons We can share Your personal information
Does the Credit Union Share?
Can You limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
YES
NO
For our marketing purposes—
to offer our products and services to you
YES
YES
For joint marketing3 with other financial companies
YES
NO
For UFCU Affiliates'1 everyday business purposes— information about your transactions and experiences
YES
NO
For UFCU Affiliates'1 everyday business purposes—
information about your creditworthiness
YES
YES
For UFCU Affiliates1 to market to you
YES
YES
For Nonaffiliates2 to market to you
YES
YES
To limit Our sharing
Call Member Services at (512) 467-8080 or Toll-Free at (800) 252-8311 - our menu will prompt you through your choice(s) or
Visit us online: www.ufcu.org/privacy
Please note:
If You are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we discontinue sharing of your information as described in this notice.
Questions?
Call Member Services at (512) 467-8080 or Toll-Free at (800) 252-8311 or go to www.ufcu.org/privacy
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?
University Federal Credit UnionFinancial Services, DBA UFCU Insurance Services
UFCU Real Estate Services
What We do
How does University Federal Credit Union protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use physical, electronic and procedural security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does University Federal Credit Union collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
open an account or deposit or withdraw money
pay your bills using UFCU's Bill Pay feature
apply for a loan or insurance
use your credit or debit card
give us your contact information
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, UFCU Affiliates, or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for UFCU Affiliates' everyday business purposes-information about your creditworthiness
Affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for Nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional
rights to limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?
Your choices will apply to everyone on your account, and may be subject to change if additional instruction is given to us by an other owner of your account.
Definitions
1 UFCU Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Our Affiliates include financial companies, such as UFCU Financial Services, LLC doing business as UFCU Insurance Services, a wholly-owned Affiliate of University Federal Credit Union and UFCU Real Estate Services, LLC doing business as Member Home Advisor, a wholly-owned Affiliate of University Federal Credit Union.
2 Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control; commonly known as "third party vendors". They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. Nonaffiliates provide benefits or services to UFCU, and members on behalf of UFCU.
3 Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between UFCU or UFCU Affiliate and a Nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include financial services companies (such as insurance agencies and organizations with whom we have agreements to jointly market financial products).
UFCU Privacy Policy Form
You may elect to stop all marketing from UFCU, its affiliated and nonaffiliated companies by completing this form. If you have previously notified us of your election, no further action is required.
Your UFCU account number(s):
Click to add
(?)
Click to add
(?)
Click to add
(?)
Your name:
Click to add
(?)
Street address:
Click to add
(?)
City:
Click to add
(?)
State:
Click to add
(?)
Zip code:
Click to add
(?)
Phone number:
Click to add
Optional
(?)
Prioritize Your Security Visit our security center to learn about fraud, privacy, and security.
